This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Initial
Raise up your hands high.
Raise up your hands　高く [Everybody gonna tell you I can't stop]
(Everybody now raise your hands)
Take hold, there's a brand new tomorrow.
掴め　Brand new tomorrow [You don't stop]
(You don't stop)
It's a beautiful eternal dream...
風の中で　自分を知る　ずっと最高のDreamだろう
...where you learn about yourself.
(Let's go)
Oh[Let's go] Oh[Let's go]
Oh
Oh (Let's go)
Oh, raise up your hands now.
Oh raise up you can't stop
If you think you're lucky just to be alive go for the highest stake in the gamble.
生きてるだけで何やろうかな
Gamble on　迫る鼓動にテンバリ
同じMission　同じ一生
Same mission creates similar lives.
But your passion for your dream will make a difference.
どんだけ夢熱いかが勝負だろ
You can never use the escalator.
Escalator　無しの永遠
But you can build up your strength, yeah yeah.
足腰鍛え　Let's begin yeah
You must eventually climb the stairs.
どうせのぼる階段
Customize them the way you like.
心こっちにCustomizeしちゃえばいい
Intense days go by.
削られて　過ぎる毎日[But you know]
Intense days go by. (But you know?)
Just laugh it off, 'cause it's a game worth competing.
攻めがいのあるGameと　笑い飛ばして
Let's see how fast you can do it
Let's see how fast you can do it.
Raise up your hands forever.
Raise up your hands　ずっと [Everybody gonna tell you I can't stop]
(Everybody now raise your hands up)
Run, sleepless challenger.
走れ　Sleepless challenger [You don't stop]
(You don't stop)
It's a quest of the never-ending dream...
今に生きる　理由を探す
夢尽きないQuest
...where you now search for the reason to live.
(Let's go)
Oh[Let's go] Oh[Let's go]
Oh
Oh (Let's go)
Oh, raise up your hands now.
Oh raise up you can't stop
After graduating from high school, Fujiwara Takumi joined the Project D team organized by Takahashi Ryosuke, and won victories as a downhill specialist in out-of-prefecture races in Tochigi, Saitama and Ibaraki, along with the hill-climber Takahashi Keisuke.
However, Takumi's race against his last opponent, Joshima Toshiya of Purple Shadow,
ended on a bitter note with his winning in the overall results, but losing in the battle.
やっぱり 片手だと違和感がある
I really do feel awkward with just one hand.
I won't be able to respond fast enough
if something unexpected happens.
何かあった時 これだとどうしても対応が遅れる
ワンハンドステアというのは
One-hand steering only works...
...when you're absolutely
confident in your driving...
限界に近い走りをしながらも
...while anticipating the future with 100% accuracy,
even when pushing yourself to the limit.
次に起こることが100%予測できていて
絶対に破綻しないという確信があってこそのテクニックだ
涼介さんの言う通りだ
It's exactly like Ryosuke said.
Without having 100% confidence
in controlling everything...
全てを100%コントロールできる自信がなきゃ
...you can't fight a battle like this.
これでバトルなんてできる訳ないよな
Tofu
Shop
配達終わったぜ
I'm done with the delivery.
Good job.
御苦労
I'm taking a nap
before going to work.
じゃ 俺一眠りしてから会社行くから
Where are you going next ?
今度はどこだ
There's no race this week because
the Eight-Six has to be repaired.
今週は休み ハチロクの修理があるから
The last battle will be
in Ibaraki next weekend.
来週が茨城の最終戦
After that, we'll head to Kanagawa.
それが終わったら神奈川だってさ
大変だよ 遠いから
Going that far is gonna be a pain.
いよいよだな
You're finally going
to face real difficulties.
本当に厳しいのはここからだろう
Fateful Encounter
拓海
Takumi.
よう 拓海
Yo, Takumi.
What's up ?
おいっす
Hi, Iketani, and you too, Kenji.
どうも 池谷先輩 健二先輩も
I feel sorry for you,
since it's still hot at night.
大変ですね 夜になっても涼しくならなくて
Hey, don't treat me like Kenji.
おいおい健二と一緒にしないでくれよ
I'm working, but he's just goofing off.
俺は働いてるけど こいつ暇なだけだからよ
What's with you ?
なんだよ そういう言い方はねぇだろう 池谷
Can't you put it a little differently, Iketani ?
Right.
そうですよ 健二先輩はデートする相手がいないだけ
Kenji has no date to spend time with.
Shut up !
うるせー 走り屋に女はいらねぇんだよー
Street racers don't need girls !
って 何度目だよこの台詞
How many times have I said that ?
Hey, when will your Eight-Six be ready ?
You're doing more mods again, aren't you ?
おい 新しいハチロクってまだなのかよ
色々弄ってるんだろ
This time, the main issue is the suspension, and the tire size is being changed, too.
今回のメインは足回りなんで
タイヤのサイズを変えたり
And strengthening the chassis
plus the reduction of weight...
ボディーの剛性アップに軽量化
You're leaving the looks completely unchanged, but modding what's inside, huh ?
外形がまったく変えずに中身に手を入れるってわけか
I wonder what kind
of car it's going to be ?
いったいどんな車になるんでしょうかね
It's awesome !
Totally awesome !
すげー 凄過ぎるよ
なんだって 連戦連勝
After all, you are Project D's undefeated downhill ace, with an uninterrupted series of victories.
無敗のプロジェクトDのダウンヒルエースだからな
Oh, that's right, Takumi.
あー そうだ 拓海
Do you go on trips with Takahashi Keisuke,
other than Project D's expeditionary races ?
あのさ プロジェクトDの遠征以外で
高橋啓介とつるんで走りに行くことなんてあるのか
Huh ?
はー いや それはないですけど
Um, no, I don't.
What made you ask that, Kenji ?
何でそんなこと聞くんですか 健二先輩
My friend's friend apparently raved about meeting Project D's double aces last weekend, on a mountain pass in Saitama.
いや 実は知合いの知合いがさ
先週埼玉の峠でプロジェクトDのダブルエースに会ったって
えらく興奮して話してたらしいんだよ
What ?
えっ 行ってませんよ そんなとこ
I never went somewhere like that.
I thought so.
だよなー 俺もおかしいと思ったんだ
It didn't sound right.
Then what the heck's going on ?
でも それってどういうことだ
Mistaken for someone else ?
誰か人違いじゃないっすか
Higashi-Chichibu
キープアンドターン
Heel and toe !
How was that, Takumi ?
どうだ 拓海 いつかは俺もこのレビンでダウンヒルデビューすんだ
Someday, I'll emerge as
a downhiller with my Levin.
That's my dream.
それが夢だな
Reality is harsh.
現実は厳しいからな
What ?
What do you mean ?
なんだよ それ
I'm not talking about you.
おまえの事言ったんじゃないよ
You know I drive around town for
deliveries during the daytime, right ?
俺さー 運送の仕事で昼間外走るじゃん
When I see middle and high school kids
having fun, that thought pops into my head.
高校生とか中学生が楽しそうに遊んでるの見る度思うんだけどさ
Uh-huh.
うん
I've come to think that
summer break is incredible.
よく考えてみると凄いよなー 夏休みって
You can play around every day.
毎日何もしないで遊んでていいんだから
Now that I've got a job,
I feel such a stark difference.
社会人になるとすごいギャップ感じるよ
I see.
そっか 去年は俺たちも夏休みだったんだよな
We had summer break last year.
One year makes a huge difference, doesn't it ?
たった一年で凄い違いだよ
It makes me sad to think that we'll never have
such a summer break again for the rest of our lives.
これからの人生で二度とあんな夏休みがないと思うと悲しいよ
Hey, do you miss...
おまえさ 寂しくないのかよ
...Natsuki ?
夏樹ちゃんの事
俺が地元に残んなきゃいけないって言ってた訳は
The reason I said
I have to stay here...
新しいチームに入って色んなことを勉強したいからなんだ
...is because I want to join
a new team and learn a lot.
I think that will bring
me closer to my dream.
そうする事が自分の夢に少しでも近づく方法だと思う
You wanted to go to Tokyo, didn't you ?
お前 東京に行きたかったんだろう
Then you have to go, no matter what.
だったら絶対行かなきゃだめだって
If you don't do what you want because
you let a temporary emotion take control...
一時的な感情に流されて
自分のやりたいと思ってた事やらなかったら
後々になって絶対後悔する時が来るんじゃないかな
...you'll eventually come
to regret it in the future.
Well, I guess I did for
a while, but I'm over it.
それは最初の内は少し
でももう吹っ切れた
I don't feel lonely.
別に寂しくなんてないよ
She went to Tokyo to pursue her dream.
あいつはあいつの夢に向かって東京へ行ったんだから
Is that so ?
そんなもんかな
I'm honestly rooting for her
as she chases her dream.
今では素直にあいつの夢を応援してやってるよ
Do you come to this mountain pass often ?
よく来るのかこの峠
ここは二回目かな
This is the second time, I guess.
It's boring to only drive on Akina.
秋名ばっかだと飽きてくるからさ
What ?!
えー うっそー
Seriously ?!
I wonder what's going on.
何かな 盛り上ってるみたいだけど
They're getting excited for some reason.
プロジェクトDのダブルエースが来るらしいぞ
I heard Project D's
double aces are coming !
えっ マジかよ すげー
Really ?
Awesome !
見に行こうぜ
Let's go see !
Yeah !
あー
How could that be possible ?
はっ どういうこと
No idea.
さっぱり分かんねぇ
げっ パンダトレノと黄色のFD
A panda Trueno and a yellow FD !
W...what the...?
なんだ
あのロゴ入りTシャツは
T-shirts with logos ?
しかもお揃い あんなの見たことないぞ
And dressed the same way ?
I've never seen anything like that.
あの すみません プロジェクトDの高橋さんと藤原さんですよね
Excuse me, but you are Takahashi
and Fujiwara of Project D, aren't you ?
Hold on.
待ってくれ 悪いけど その質問にはイエスともノーとも答えない事にするよ
I'm sorry, but I can't answer
yes or no to that question.
分かるだろ 今日は公式の遠征でここに来た訳じゃないからさ
You see, we didn't come
here for an official visit.
In other words, this is supposed to be a secret, so we don't want to create a buzz.
つまり お忍びって事なんで あまり騒がれたくないんだよね
Right, Keisuke ?
なっ啓介
うん
He's acting so casual with Keisuke.
啓介とか言って呼び捨てにしてるし
しかも啓介 背が低すぎるし
Besides, that Keisuke is too short.
いいのかよ 拓海 あんなのほっといて
Hey, is it okay for you to let
them do whatever they want ?
It's obvious they're imposters.
明らかに偽モンじゃん
Okay or not, I don't want to get involved.
いいも悪いもできれば関わりたくない
They're too embarrassing to watch.
見てる方が恥ずかしいよ
Excuse me.
あのー すみません
Do you mind if I take a picture with you ?
一緒に写真を撮って下さい
Yay !
女に持ててる ふざけんな もう許せん
They're popular with girls.
Screw it.
I can't stand this.
Now I'm gonna be in trouble.
いやー 参ったなー
Hey imposter !
おーい 偽者
誰だ お前は
Who the hell are you ?
Hey, that's what I want to ask you.
ふん こっちこそ誰だと聞きたいね
What ?
なんだと
What do you mean ?
何が言いたいんだ
I know you're not with Project D !
俺は知ってるんだよ
あんた達はプロジェクトDなんかじゃないって事を
えっマジで
何を根拠に
What makes you say that
we're not with Project D ?
俺たちがプロジェクトDじゃないと
I have proof, which is....
証拠ならあるね
なぜならば隣にいるこいつこそ本物の藤原拓海だからだい
...this guy next to me.
He's the real Fujiwara Takumi !
なにー
Say what ?
うっそくせー
It sounds so fake.
We have proof.
証拠ならあるぜ
Hey, Takumi, show them your license.
おい 拓海 免許証出してみ
Um...
えっとー あっ 車ん中に置いてきた
I left it in the car.
What the...?!
バカ そんな大事な物をなぜ持ち歩かないんだよ
You moron !
How come you're not carrying
such an important thing ?!
Oh, I get it.
あっはん 分かったぜ
You guys are imposters.
お前らこそ偽者じゃないか
Looks like you've got
a Levin, which is so bogus.
見た所 随分インチキくさいレビンに乗ってるようだが
Say what ?!
何を インチキくさい
Bogus ?
Fujiwara Takumi drives a panda Trueno...
藤原拓海といえばパンダトレノだろう ほれほれ
...like that.
He's right ! You're a fake !
そうだそうだ
インチキ野郎
You're an imposter !
帰れ 偽者
何だと 失礼な
What was that ?
That's rude !
あー こうなるんじゃないかと思ったよ
I knew it.
I had a bad feeling that
something like this would happen.
嫌な予感してた
The real Trueno is being repaired !
本物のトレノはな 今修理してるところなんだ
The suspension was damaged when the car hit
the curb during the last downhill battle in Ibaraki !
前回の茨城遠征の時ダウンヒル場取で縁石に当てて
足回りが壊れたんだよ
えっへん どうだ 驚いたか
Well ? Surprised ?
Only the real person knows that.
本物だけが知る情報だぜ
Hey, keep your mouth
shut if you don't know.
滅多の事を言ってもらいたくない
With all due respect, I, Fujiwara Takumi,
am famous for my precise vehicle control.
憚りながらこの藤原拓海
針の穴を通す正確無比な車のコントロールが売りなんてね
I'd never hit the curb and
damage my car during a battle.
バトルの最中に縁石に当てて車を壊すなんて事は
俺に限ってありえねぇ
おー 最高 さすが
What the hell is with him ?
なんだ こいつは
今日の所は見なかったことにしておいてやるけど
I'll forget what I saw today...
...so never pretend to be us again.
二度と俺たちの名を騙ることはしないでくれよ
行こうか 啓介
Let's go, Keisuke.
てめーら ふざけんな 待て こらー
Don't mess around with us !
Hey, wait !
何 偽者に会った
What ?
You met the imposters ?!
Yes.
はい
It's just as I thought,
there are imposters out there.
やっぱりそうか
偽者がいるんだ どうも変だと思ったぜ
Excuse me.
あの すみません
I want to see Mr. Fujiwara Takumi.
藤原拓海さんに会いたいんですけど
ここにくればプロジェクトDの藤原さんに連絡が着くって
I've been told that I could contact
Mr. Fujiwara of Project D if I came here.
聞いてきたんですけど
Are you Mr. Fujiwara of Project D ?
あなたがプロジェクトDの藤原さん
Yes, I am.
そうだけど
Personally, I don't have a grudge
against you, but that was for Tomoko.
直接あなたに恨みはないけど　これはトモコの分だよ
身に覚えがあるでしょう？
You should know what I'm talking about.
Who is this Tomoko girl ?
だれだよ　トモコって　知らねえけど
I have no idea.
Acting like you know nothing ?
シラをきるつもりなの？
そういうとこ　本当に男らしくないよね
You're such a coward.
まあまあ　落ち着きなよ
Now, now.
Just calm down.
I don't know what's going on,
but we should talk this out.
どういう事情が知らないけど　話せばわかるって
You guys are his friends, right ?
あなたたちもこの人の仲間でしょう
I can't trust you, and I have no
intention of talking to you either.
信用できないし　話し合うつもりもないよ
Hey, don't be so stubborn.
そ　そんなことを言ってたら
In any case, he tricked my close
friend and now she's miserable.
とにかく　この人はあたしの大切な友達を騙して
哀しませてるの
I admit that my friend was
careless for pursuing you...
そりゃ　ナンパされたあたしの友達も　ちょっと軽率だけど
根は純粋ですごく素直ないい子なの
...but she's a good, honest person.
I can't stand a guy who'd take advantage of his fame to play around with a girl's heart !
ちょっとぐらい有名だからって　有頂天になって
女の子の気持ちを弄んだりする男は許せないの
That's dishonest and horrible !
不誠実だし最低だよ
That's all I wanted to say.
言いたいことはいったし　もう帰ります
Good bye.
いえいえ　そうじゃなくてさ
Oh, come on.
Are you sure this is the
guy who hit on your friend ?
君の友達をナンパしたのは　本当にここにいるこいつだったのかな
うん？
How can I be ?
俺の訳ないじゃないですか　冗談じゃないっすよ池谷先輩
This is ridiculous, right, Iketani ?
I know.
わかってるって　例のニセモノがやったに決まってんだ
It must be that imposter.
Imposter ?
ニセモノ？
Right.
そうなんだよ　こいつのニセモノがいるんだ　デブでブサイクなのが！
There's is an imposter,
who's chubby and ugly.
嘘くさい　そんな話　絶対信じない
It sounds so fake...
I can't believe a story like that.
とにかく　こいつかどうか確認してみてくれよ
Regardless, double-check
and see if it's really him.
こいつの写真を撮ってメールで君の友達に送って見せれば
You can find out whether he's the same person or not by just snapping a picture and mailing it to your friend.
同じ人物かどうか　分かるじゃないか
If you insist...
そこまで言うなら
電話つながらない　電波の届かないとこにいるのかなあ
She's not responding.
I wonder if she's out of the area.
一応メールだけ送っておくけど
I'll send her a mail, though.
なあんだよ　すっきりしないなあ
What a bummer.
I have to go now.
あたし　もう行かなきゃ 電車の時間あるから
I've got to catch the train.
こうなることを心配してたんだ
This's exactly what
I was worried about.
Those imposters have a lot
of nerve hitting on girls.
ニセモノのくせに女の子をナンパしてるなんて
図々しいにもほどがあるぜ
I don't know what's going on.
何がなんだかわけ分かんないっすよ　おれ
How can this be happening to me...?
なんでこんなことになるのか
You'd better let Takahashi
Ryosuke know about this, Takumi.
この件は　高橋涼介の耳に入といたほうがいいかもしれないぞ　拓海
もしもし　藤原か　どうした？
Hello ?
Oh, Fujiwara, what's up ?
There are imposters ?
ニセモノが出没してる？
Yeah, I heard a little about
that from another source.
ああ　その件なら別のところからもちらほら情報が挙がってる
Yes, and...
そうなんです　それで
What ? Really ?
なに　本当か　そんな悪さをしてるようならほっとけないな
If it's that bad, we can't
leave them alone, can we ?
わかったよ　こっちからも動いてみる
I understand.
I'll get right on it.
Don't worry.
心配するな　俺たちのネットワークを使えば
If we use our network...
ねずみを捕捉するのに　そう時間はかからないと思うよ　任せておけ
...it shouldn't take too long to catch these rats.
Leave this to me.
Anyhow, that was a real
disaster for you, wasn't it ?
それにしても災難だったよなあ　拓海は
Just forget about it.
気にすることないぜ　単なる誤解なんだし
It's just a misunderstanding.
I know that, but I feel down.
わかってけど　なんかへっこんちゃうんだよなあ
That girl was really
mad at me, wasn't she ?
さっきの女の子　本気でおれに対して怒ってたよな
I've never met a girl before
who gave me a dirty look.
女の子にあんな目で睨まれたことってないからさ
I was more shocked by
her glare than the slap.
引っ叩かれたことより　あの目がショックだったよ
Personally, I don't have any grudge
against you, but that was for Tomoko.
直接あなたに恨みはないけど　これはトモコの分だよ
You should know what I'm talking about.
身に覚えがあるでしょう？
何だよこれ　いらいらするような　いても立ってもいられない気分
What's wrong with me ?
I feel so antsy, but
I don't know what to do.
I don't get it.
わけわかんねえよ
もしもし　トモコ？美佳だよ　写真見た？
Hello, Tomoko ?
This is Mika.
Did you see the picture ?
Wha...?
え？ぜんぜん違う顔？
Totally different face ?!
そんな　もう一度よく見てよ
No way !
Take a look at it carefully.
You know, he might
look different in a photo...
ほら　写真ってさ　写り方によっては違って見えることも
He doesn't ?
ありえない？まるで別人？
Totally different person ?!
はぁ　っていうか　「はぁ」　じゃないんだけど　やっちゃったよあたし
Okay...
No, not okay.
Oh crap, I...
関係ない人にフルスイングかましちゃったあ
I gave a full swing slap
to a totally different person !
ありがとうございました　今日も暑いなあ
Thank you for coming !
Another hot day.
ええ　そうかな
You really think so ?
It's totally possible.
いや　ありえると思うよ　絶対
I'm sure of it.
なんの話ですか　先輩
What are you talking about ?
Well, it's about the girl from yesterday.
いや　昨日の女の子のことなんだけどさ
あの子と拓海がいい感じなんじゃないかって
He says her and Takumi
would make a nice couple.
Think about it.
だってよ　出会いとしてはドラマチックだしさ
Their first meeting was so dramatic.
My instincts tell me that there
was a spark between them.
これはおれの勘なんだけどねえ
二人の間にはびびっと来るものがあったんじゃないかなあ
Now that you mention it, Takumi was still upset about the incident later.
そう言われてみれば　拓海もやたらと気にしてましたよ　あの後
You see, you see ?
だろうだろう？
Of course he was.
そりゃ気にすると思うよ　拓海じゃなくても
Anyone would be.
She threw a slap all of a sudden, and left.
いきなり引っ叩いて帰っちゃうんだから
「バケーン！」　ですからねえ
SLLAAAP, just like that.
That could be the end.
でもそれきりってことも
I don't think this is over.
いや　それきりってことはないと思うなあ　勘だよ　勘
It's just a hunch.
もしもし　涼介　おれだけど
Hi, is this Ryosuke ?
It's me.
The Eight-Six is ready, and
I'm going to take it to him.
ハチロク仕上がったよ　今から藤原に届けにいく
そうか　こちからも連絡しようと思ってたんだ
Okay.
I was going to call
you about that matter.
I found the tag number of the imposter's car.
この前の件だけど　ニセモノの車のナンバーが割れたよ
Huh ? Already ?
え　もうか？
I don't have the time, so I'll
let Keisuke take care of this.
おれはちょっと時間ないから　この件は啓介に任せることにした
I told him not to get too rough, but can you
watch over him while following up on the matter ?
あまり手荒なことはしないように言ってあるんだけど
啓介の監視の意味も込めて
そっちのほう　フォローしてもらえないかな
Okay, you can count on me.
わかった　任せてくれ
Also, it's a little early, but I'll recon the Kanagawa area with Kenta tomorrow.
ああ　それから　ちょっと気が早いけど
賢太を連れて　明日神奈川の偵察に行ってくる
I see.
そうか　いよいよだな
The time has come.
Project D is getting closer
to entering its final stage.
俺たちプロジェクトDも
ついに最終ステージの入り口に差し掛かろうとしているわけだ
感無量ってとこかな
I feel fulfilled.
The real challenge begins now.
こっからが正念場だけどな　いつもより念入りにコースの下見をしてくる
I'll check the courses
more carefully than usual.
Okay.
ああ　茨城遠征もあと一戦
We have one last race in Ibaraki.
That next hurdle isn't very high.
こんどの相手のハードルはそう高くはない
Once it's over, Kanagawa, also known as
the holy ground of street racing, will be next.
これが終われば 走りの聖地とまで言われる神奈川
The battles will be unimaginably tough...
想像以上の厳しい戦いになるだろうが
...but once we overcome the challenge, the true
meaning of "D" in Project D will become apparent.
そうれを乗り越えたときこそ
プロジェクトDの「D」に込められた本当の意味が見えてくる
Are you Mr. Fujiwara of Project D ?
プロジェクトDの藤原さんってあんたか
Who the hell are you ?
なんだよ　おまえは
I'm just a noob.
My name is Akiyama Wataru.
おれは　まあ　秋山渉ってけちなもんなんだけど
Hey, chill out.
I just wanna have a friendly talk.
そう身構えないで　友好的に話そうぜ
I'm not picking a fight or anything.
別に喧嘩を売ろうってわけじゃないんだ
See ?
We're both Eight-Six drivers.
同じハチロク乗りじゃないか
I, um...how do I put it ?
おれもさ　なんて言うかなあ
As an Eight-Six driver, I'm very interested in the driving of the famous Fujiwara Takumi.
ハチロク乗りの端くれとしちゃあ
天下に名高い藤原拓海の走りには一方ならぬ感心があるんだよなあ
I wonder if you'd show me
your incredible driving technique.
ちょっと見せてもらえないのかな　あんたのすげえドラテクを
No, I'm not supposed to do that.
だめだ　それはできないことに
Just one flashy drift, please.
派手なドリフトを頼みますよ
My request is that you burst out sideways
from the top of that bridge over there, then...
おれのリクエストとしては
その橋の上から　ドーンと横になって飛び出してきてもらって
それから…
できないったら　涼介に止められてるんだ
I can't.
Ryosuke won't allow that.
出口が直角に曲がってるんで
The exit is a 90-degree bend, so if you can clear the
corner with only accelerator work, the crowd will go nuts.
アクセルワークだけで　ギョワワワーンとクリアしてくれたら
喝采もんですよ
On-the-line cornering, you see ?
ビシーとラインも決めて
Don't screw around with me !
ふざけんな　簡単に言うな！
It's not as easy as you think !
There's no such god-like driver
who can do it on the first try !
そんな神技みたいなことを　一発でやれる人間がいるわけないだろう！
You're right.
その通り　普通は絶対無理
Normally, it's impossible...
Here he comes.
来たな
But I guess the world is big, and there's one
moron who can pull it off without any practice.
だけど世の中広いって言うか
リハもしないで一発で決めてしまうバカがいるんだよなあ　一人だけ
Only one.
さて　皆さんお立ち合い
Alright, listen guys.
You'd better pay attention and watch what's gonna happen very carefully.
これだけは本当に　目ん玉引ん剥いてよく見ておいたほうがいいぜ
You don't get to see it this close very often.
こんな近くで直に見られるチャンスは滅多にないから
This is real drifting.
これぞ　本当のドリフト
Shit, a panda Trueno !
パンダトレノ！
速い　あいつめ　またさらにすごみが増してやがんな
So fast.
He's much better than before.
What was that ?
今のは　なんだ
Could it be the real one ?
まさか本物
It must be.
そうとしか考えられないだろ
あんなことができるハチロクが　ほかにいるわけないし
No other Eight-Six could do that.
急用を思い出した　帰るぞ啓介
I just remembered
some urgent business.
Let's go, Keisuke.
Okay.
お…おお
偶然だな　あんたも啓介って言うのか　おれもなんだ
What a coincidence.
Your name is Keisuke, huh ?
Mine, too.
It's been a while, Wataru.
久しぶりだな　渉
Yeah. It looks like you're doing alright.
そっちも元気そうだな
本物だったのね！
He was the real...!
さてと　どうする　こいつら
Now, what should we do with them ?
What gets me most is that
they used Project D's name.
一番許せねえのは　プロジェクトDの名を騙ってることだ
The team's fame is like a medal of honor.
We managed to build it with the entire team's dedication.
チームの名声はメンバー全員が死に物狂いで勝ち続け築き上げてきた
勲章みたいなものだからな
すみません　許してください
We're sorry !
Please forgive us !
それから二番目に許せねえのは
The second problem...
...is that my imposter is incredibly ugly.
おれのニセモノがあまりにもブサイクなことなんだよな
最低でも骨の一本や二本
That deserves a few broken bones...
Sorry that I'm so ugly !
ブサイクでごめんなさい
チッ　冗談だよ
Just kidding.
We won't resort to violence or anything,
but make sure you never do this again.
手荒なことはしない
ただし　こんな悪ふざけはもうこれっきりにしてくれよ
ナンバーから住所氏名もわかるんだ　おれたちの情報網を甘く見ないことだ
We can get your name and
address from the tag number.
Don't underestimate our information network.
I'll never do it again !
もうしません
Being in Project D was my dream !
夢だったんです　プロジェクトDになることが
そうだ　藤原　おまえからもこいつらに言いたいことがあるんだろう
Oh, Fujiwara, you have something
you wanted to tell them, right ?
あのさ　トモコっていう女の子をナンパしたでしょう
Um...
...you picked up a girl
named Tomoko, didn't you ?
I got in trouble because of that.
そのせいでおれが恨まれてるんだよね
Make sure you contact her, and
clear up this misunderstanding...
ちゃんと連絡取って　その子に謝って　誤解を解いておいてもらえるかな
...since it's been a real pain for me.
ものすごい迷惑だから
I will !
やります　やります　本当にすみませんでした
I'm very sorry !
Make sure you do it.
ちゃんとやってくれないと困るよ君
Okay.
はは！
さすが地元だけにクルマなりによく乗れてるけどな
As you'd expect from a local, he's pretty good for what his car is capable of.
I wonder how far Project D will go.
どれだけやれるかな　プロジェクトD
We'll show them we're out of their league.
走りの聖地　神奈川エリアのレベルの違いを思い知らせてやるぜ
The Kanagawa area is known as
the holy ground of street racing.
Fujiwara Takumi:
Takahashi Ryosuke:
Takahashi Keisuke:
Uehara Mika:
Miki Shinichiro
Koyasu Takehito
Seki Tomokazu
Hayami Saori
Takeuchi Itsuki:
Iketani Koichiro:
Kenji:
Akiyama Wataru:
Iwata Mitsuo
Yao Kazuki
Takagi Wataru
Matsumoto Yasunori
Fake Takumi:
Fake Keisuke:
Hojo Gou:
Fumihiro:
Man A:
Girl A:
Girl B:
Katsu Anri
Miura Hirokazu
Kiuchi Hidenobu
Hosoi Hajime
Maeda Hiroki
Sato Megumi
Sugiura Naoko
Fujiwara Bunta:
Ishizuka Unsho
Falling perfect lighten the focal
Following the brake light of the front car.
A shimmering light up ahead in the dark street.
暗い道の先にぼんやりにじむ明かり
It's the silence like a silent film.
If the tires strike a silent wind
A
Central Anime
Production
Translation:
Hiro-kun
Timing:
Todd Perkins
Editing:
Barbara
Todd Perkins
Brain
Dave
Mouse
The light was all I could depend on.
頼りになるものはそれしか見えなかった
I felt like I could catch it...
この並木道を抜けていけばきっと
...if I passed through this tree-lined street.
つかめるような気がした
Get up! I just can't understand.
Give up! I just can't understand
I couldn't find what I'd been looking for.
外にはまだ捜し物は何もなくて
Yeah, it starts at this moment.
Yeah! It stops at this moment
At this place.
この場所から
Please turn over the flyleaf.
Please stand alone on the flyleaf
I lost my way.
I lost my way
白く曇った窓と的外れなNavigation
Fogged up windows, and...
...messed up navigation.
As the stoplight turns red...
赤く変わった信号で
サイドミラーに映る視界を遮るLight
...a light in the side mirror blinds my eyes.
I gradually close the window...
冷たい風が入り込まないように
窓をそっと締めたんだ
...to stop the cold wind from blowing in.
Get up! I just can't understand.
Give up! I just can't understand
We must choose one of the paths that lie ahead.
そこに広がる道を選んで進む僕は
Yeah, it starts at this moment.
Yeah! It stops at this moment
Because you're with me.
君がいるなら
Please turn over the flyleaf.
Please stand alone on the flyleaf